Ohh! You're so wrapped up in layers, onion boy, you're afraid of your own feelings.
你把自己包裹了好几层 你害怕你自己的感觉
- Go away! - There you are, doing it again just like you did to Fiona.
- 走开 - 你又那么做了
All she ever do was like you, maybe even love you.
就像对公主一样 她喜欢你 也许是爱你
Love me? She said I was ugly, a hideouscreature.
爱我  她说我是一个丑八怪
I heard the two of you talking.
我听见你们两个的谈话了
She wasn't talking about you. She was talking about, uh, somebody else.
她不是说你 她不是说你 还有别人
She wasn't talking about me?
她不是说我
Well, then who was she talking about?
那她说的是谁
-Uh-uh, no way. I ain't saying anything. You don't wanna listen to me.  Right? Right?  -Donkey!
-我不会说一个字 反正你也没有兴趣听 真的吗 真的吗- 驴子
- No! - Okay, look.
- 不 - 好吧
I'm sorry, all right?
抱歉 还好吗
I'm sorry.
抱歉
I guess I am just a big, stupid, ugly ogre.
好吧 我是一个愚蠢而又丑陋的妖怪
Can you forgive me?
你能原谅我吗
Hey, that's what friends are for, right?
这就是作为朋友应该的 对吗
Right. Friends?
正确 朋友
So, um,
这样啊
what did Fiona say about me?
公主是怎么说我的
What are you asking me for? Why don't you just go ask her?
你为什么问我 你应该去问她
The wedding! We'll never make it in time Ha-ha-ha! Never fear, for where there's a will, there's a way,and I have a way.
婚礼 我们别错过这个 别急 有志者事竟成  我有办法